{
    "questionBank": [
      {
        "question": "What is a Schmeckle?",
        "a": "Ricks favorite food",
        "b": "A currency",
        "c": "The name of fly-guards",
        "d": "Ricks Cat-person friend",
        "correctAnswer": "b"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT one of Rick catch phrases?",
        "a": "No jumping in the sewer.",
        "b": "GRASSSSS... tastes bad!",
        "c": "Hit the deck, Jack!",
        "d": "Uh ohhhh! Somersoult jump!",
        "correctAnswer": "c"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the dimension of the original Rick?",
        "a": "C-126",
        "b": "C-132",
        "c": "C-129",
        "d": "C-137",
        "correctAnswer": "d"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of Mortys High School?",
        "a": "Beerwah State High School",
        "b": "Harry Herpson High School",
        "c": "Gene Vegan High School",
        "d": "FIU",
        "correctAnswer": "b"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of Jerrys favorite Rick?",
        "a": "Doofus",
        "b": "Roofus",
        "c": "Goofus",
        "d": "Rick G-506",
        "correctAnswer": "a"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of Ricks ex-wife?",
        "a": "Diane",
        "b": "Janet",
        "c": "Joyce",
        "d": "Ellen",
        "correctAnswer": "a"
      },
      {
        "question": "What job does Beth have?",
        "a": "Chef",
        "b": "Novel Writer",
        "c": "Astronomer",
        "d": "Horse Surgeon",
        "correctAnswer": "d"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does wubba lubba dub dub mean?",
        "a": "I'm a genius",
        "b": "Let's party",
        "c": "Please leave",
        "d": "I'm in great pain",
        "correctAnswer": "d"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who killed Birdperson in a horrific turnabout during his wedding?",
        "a": "Jerry",
        "b": "Summer",
        "c": "Tammy",
        "d": "Beth",
        "correctAnswer": "c"
      },
      {
        "question": "What species is Morty's son?",
        "a": "Smarkian",
        "b": "Gazorpazorp",
        "c": "Cromulan",
        "d": "Human",
        "correctAnswer": "b"
      }
    ]
  }